Guide to the Boniface I. Obichere papers, 1959-1996
Obichere, Boniface I. papers, 1959-1996
- Series V. Journal of African Studies
  - Journal of African Studies
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.7, Nos.2-4, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 78)
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.8, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 79)
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.9, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 80)
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.10, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.11, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.12, Nos.1-2, 4, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.13, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.14, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Series VI. African Studies Center (ASC)
  - General
    - "African Studies Center — General", 1972-Aug. 1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - "African Studies Center — General", Sept.-Nov. 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - "African Studies Center — General", 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Faculty and employee lists, 1970-1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - List of faculty publications, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Summary information on faculty, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Mailing List, Nov. 12, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Guides to Undergraduate and Graduate Study in History, 1972-1973, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - African Studies programs: General and undergraduate, 1968-1977 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Master of Arts in African Area Studies, 1967-1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Doctorate in African Literature, 1972-1975 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Extension Certificate in African Studies, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Black Studies program, Federal City College: Course list, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - University of Maryland: Proposal for a Masters of Arts in African American Studies, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Budget
    - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Budget, 1973-1974, 1973, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Committees
    - Ad hoc Review Committee for Evaluation of the African Studies Center, 1973-Jan. 1974 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Ad hoc Review Committee for Evaluation of the African Studies Center, Feb. 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Executive Committee for the Afro-American Studies Center, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Advisory Committee for the Center for Afro-American Studies, 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Advisory Committee for the Center for Afro-American Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Advisory Committee for the James S. Coleman African Studies Center, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Operating Committee: Applications for a Research Assistant for the Center for Afro-American Studies, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 24-26)
    - Search Committee: Director of African Studies Center, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Reports
    - Small reports on the aims, objectives, and activities of the African Studies Center (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Report on minorities at UC Berkeley, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - "Proposal for a Center for the Study of Afro-American History and Culture" (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - "A Proposal for the Establishment of a Center for the Study of Afro-American History and Culture": Redraft and Submitted proposal, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - "Appendix II" (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - "Curriculum Development", n.d. (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - "Afro-American Study Center Status Report and Recommendations, December, 1969" (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Reports on teaching about Africa, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - "Black American Studies Program: Background, Recent Developments, Enrollment Information," Southern Illinois University, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - African Studies Center Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - "Continuing Plan of Operation of the African Studies Center, 1973-74 — 1977-78" (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - African Studies Center Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - "Report to the Review Committee for Evaluation of the African Studies Center, UCLA", 1974 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Center for Russian and East European Studies Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Publications
    - African Religious Research, Vol.2, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - African Studies Center Newsletter, 1969-1978 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - African Studies Center Newsletter, 1982-1986 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - African Studies Papers, Nos.3, 5, 6, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Events: Colloquiums, Symposiums, Conferences, Lectures
    - Flyers: Lectures, Films, Dances, 1970-1994, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - African Studies Colloquium
      - Papers: Henry Bienen; Victor Olorunsola, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - States and Kingdoms in West Africa in the Nineteenth Century, symposium
      - Program and notes, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Papers: Daniel F. McCall; C.W. Newbury, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Papers: Earl Phillips; Dalbert A. Williams, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - International Law and National Development in Southern Africa, symposium
      - Program, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 43)
      - Papers: Assibi O. Abudu; Richard L. Sklar, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 43)
      - Summary of Session I and Session II, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Relationship Between African and Afro-American Studies, colloquium(?)/book
      - Notes, table of contents, introduction, conclusion, bibliography, ca.1971 (Box 25, Folder 45)
      - Paper: Klinghoffer, Arthur Jay, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 46)
      - Paper: Kuper, Leo, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 47-48)
      - Paper: Mazrui, Ali A., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 49)
      - Paper: Povey, John, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 50)
      - Paper: Ranger, T.O., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 51)
      - Paper: Ricard, Alain, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
      - Paper: Shepperson, George, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Paper: Smith, Arthur L., 1971 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Paper: Van den Berghe, Pierre L., 1971 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Paper: Vlasak, Rodney, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: The Changing Role of the Military in African Societies, colloquium
      - Flyer, outline, bibliography, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Papers: J.S. Cookey; Uma O. Eleazu; Martin Kilson, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Papers: Hilda Kuper, René Lemarchand, Robin Luckham, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Papers: Michel Martin; Terence Ranger, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Papers: Elliott P. Skinner; G.N. Uzoigwe, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Art, Artifice, and Reality in African Verbal Experience, colloquium
      - Program, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Papers: Mohammad Aminu and Rodney Vlasak; Megan Biesele; Ben G. Blount, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Papers: Robert Griffeth; Keith T. Kernan, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Papers: John U. Ogbu; David H. Spain and Spero M. Manson, Jr., 1972 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - African Systems of Forms, colloquium
      - Program, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Papers: Daniel J. Crowley; Daniel F. McCall, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Paper: Charles M.H. Keil, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Paper: Paul Reisman, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Ecological-Cultural Analysis in Tropical Rural Development, colloquium:
      - Flyer and Paper: Eduardo Cruz de Carvalho and Kenneth Ruddle, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Language and History, colloquium
      - Paper: Christopher Ehret, Gary Okihiro, Terry Stamps, Barbara Turner, Sherilyn Young, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Papers: Bernd Heine; Thomas N. Huffman, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Paper: J.E.G. Sutton, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Paper: Jan Vansina, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Higher Education and National Development in Africa, colloquium
      - Outline and Papers: Frederick S. Arkhurst; P. Diagne; Philip Foster; Thomas Knipp; Robert Koehl, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Papers: Ali A. Mazrui, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Papers: Celestine Nwacukwu; Uga Onwuka, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Papers: Barbara Anthony Rhodes, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 28)
      - Papers: Hugh H. Smythe and Louise Wunderle Schaefer; Eric James Whittle, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Double Impact — New Views on the Age of Imperialism in French-Speaking Africa
      - Paper: Leland C. Barrows, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - African States and the Military: Past and Present, conference
      - Flyer and correspondence, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Paper: Alpers, Edward A., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 32)
      - Paper: Griffeth, Robert R., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 33)
      - Paper: Gutteridge, William, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 34)
      - Paper: Olorunsola, Victor A., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 35)
      - Paper: Osuntokun, Akinjide, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 36)
      - Paper: Pinkney, Robert, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 37)
      - Paper: Smaldone, Joseph P., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Political Change in Portuguese-Speaking Africa, colloquium, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Liberalization and Democratization in Africa, mini-conference:
      - Paper: Dean E. McHenry, Jr., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 40)
      - Colloquium papers and panels, 1968, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 41-42)
- Series VII. Committees, Programs, Projects
  - Academic Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Academic Senate, 1972-1996 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Ad hoc Advisory Committee to EAP (Education Abroad Program) on African Centers (see also Education Abroad Program), 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Ad hoc Advisory Committee to EAP (Education Abroad Program) on African Centers, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Ad hoc Advisory Committee to EAP (Education Abroad Program) on African Centers, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Ad hoc Committee to Review the Nonreappointment of Assistant Professor Aliko Songolo, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Ad hoc Promotion Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Ad hoc Review Committee for Evaluation of the African Studies Center, UCLA, 1973-Jan. 1974 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Ad hoc Review Committee for Evaluation of the African Studies Center, UCLA, Feb. 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - African Studies Association, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - American Historical Association Program Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Biafra Children's Relief Committee/Peace in Biafra: Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Biafra Children's Relief Committee/ Peace in Biafra: Donation letters, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Biafra Children's Relief Committee/Peace in Biafra: Publicity and Newspaper Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Bilingual Cross-Cultural Black Specialists Program, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Book drive, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Center for Research on Economic Development, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Ethnic Studies, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Intellectual Change and Perspective in African Studies, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Committee on International and Comparative Studies (CICS), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Committee on International and Comparative Studies (CICS), 1973 Jan.-Mar. (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Committee on International and Comparative Studies (CICS), 1973 Apr.-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Committee on International and Comparative Studies (CICS), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Committee on International and Comparative Studies (CICS), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Committee on International and Comparative Studies (CICS), 1976 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Committee on International and Comparative Studies (CICS), 1977 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Committee on International and Comparative Studies (CICS), 1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Committee/Task Force on Undergraduate Goals, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Council on Educational Development (CED), 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Danfa/Ghana Comprehensive Rural Health and Family Planning Project, 1970-1975 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Department of History meetings, 1970-1985 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Education Abroad Program — Advisor's manual (see also Ad hoc Advisory Committee to EAP), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Education Abroad Program — Ghana, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Education Abroad Program — Ghana, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Education Abroad Program — Haiti, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Education Abroad Program — Nairobi, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Education Abroad Program — Nairobi, 1972-1976 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Education Abroad Program — Tanzania, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Executive Committee for the Afro-American Studies Center, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee for the Center for Afro-American Studies, 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee for the Center for Afro-American Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee for the James S. Coleman African Studies Center, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - FTE Priorities Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Council, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - High Potential Program, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 21-22)
  - Institute of Intercultural Research, n.d. (1970s) (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - KPFK Radio — "From Tribe to Nation", 11 a.m., Sept. 10, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - L.S.B. Leakey Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - L.S.B. Leakey Foundation, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - L.S.B. Leakey Foundation, 1979, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Operating Committee: Applications for a Research Assistant for the Center for Afro-American Studies, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 24-26)
  - Operation Crossroads Africa, 1961-1965 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Operation Crossroads Africa, 1966-1975 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Operation Crossroads Africa, 1976-1982 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Operation SOS (Save Our Spaceship), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Peace in Biafra (See Biafra Children's Relief Comm.)
  - Petition to Aid South African Students, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Search Committee - African Studies Professor, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Search Committee - African Studies Professor: Candidates: A-B, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Search Committee - African Studies Professor: Candidates: Barrows, Leland, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Search Committee - African Studies Professor: Candidates: C-H, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Search Committee - African Studies Professor: Candidates: Depelchin, Jacques, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 39-40)
  - Search Committee - African Studies Professor: Candidates: I-P, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Search Committee - African Studies Professor: Candidate: Miller, Joseph C., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Search Committee - African Studies Professor: Candidates: R-Sm, 1973-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Search Committee - African Studies Professor: Candidates: So-W, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Search Committee - Director of the African Studies Center, 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Senate Equal Opportunity/Academic Affirmative Action Compliance Committee, 1969, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Senate Equal Opportunity/Academic Affirmative Action Compliance Committee, 1985-1986 May (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Senate Equal Opportunity/Academic Affirmative Action Compliance Committee, 1986 June-Sept. (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Senate Equal Opportunity/Academic Affirmative Action Compliance Committee, 1986 Nov. (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Senate Equal Opportunity/Academic Affirmative Action Compliance Committee, 1986 Dec. (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Senate Equal Opportunity/Academic Affirmative Action Compliance Committee, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Special Committee for Development of Communication with Negro Colleges and Universities, 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Subcommittee to Review Interdepartmental MA Degree in Industrial Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Subcommittee to Review Neuroscience Department, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee to Review Social Science Department, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Task Force on Africa and Los Angeles Relations, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Recruitment and Development (URD) Program Selection Committee, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - United Nations: Economic Commission for Africa, Conference of African Planners, First session, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - United Nations: Economic Commission for Africa, Conference of African Planners, Second session, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 6-17)
  - United Nations: Economic Commission for Africa, Conference of African Planners, Second session, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - United Nations: Economic Commission for Africa, Conference of African Planners, Second Session: Minutes and final report, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Urban Research Group, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous committees, programs, and projects, 1970-1989 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Variuos African events: Flyers, 1968-1979 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Various African events: Flyers, 1983-1996, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Series VIII. Grants
  - Summary information on received grants and grant announcements, 1972-1978 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - The Ford Foundation
    - General correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Grant: Non-Western Area Studies Grant, University of California at Berkeley, Los Angeles, and Santa Barbara, 1960-1974: Final Report [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Grant 700-0258A: Support of the African and Near Eastern Studies Program, 1970-1979 [RESTRICTED], 1973-1979 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Grant 710-0434A: Interdisciplinary Research Project on Angola, Mozambique, and Guinea-Bissau, 1971-1975 [RESTRICTED], 1971-1976 (Box 29, Folder 6-8)
    - Grant 710-0481: History of African Religious Systems, 1971-1977 [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Research Fellowship: Research on History of the Western Sudan by Prof. Sekene M. Cissoko, 1975-1976 [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Institute of American Culture
    - Afro-Americans in Ghana, 1972-1973 [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Malcolm X and Africa [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH)
    - Grant EO-4619-71-59: Study kits on African Arts, 1974 [RESTRICTED] (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - African Humanities Institute Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Office of Education, National Defense Education Fund (NDEA)
    - Proposal for a New International Studies Program, Graduate Level, 1973-1975 [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Grant OEG-0-74-0325: African Studies Center's Area and Language Program, 1974-1979(?) [RESTRICTED], 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Proposal draft [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Proposal and revision application [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Revision application and extension application [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Extension application [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Extension application [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Title VI, National Defense Foreign Language (NDFL) Fellowships and Fulbright-Hays Fellowships [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Enrichment Program in African Studies for Junior College Instructors, 1975 [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [RESTRICTED], 1972-1995 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - UCLA and African Studies Center Grants
    - Grant and funding applications and research proposals [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous grants
    - Miscellaneous grants [RESTRICTED], 1973-1993 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Series IX. Notes and Notebooks
  - Archival research: Permissions and photocopies (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Notes: Oral tradition, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Notes: Outlines and research notes (Box 28, Folder 9-12)
  - Notes: Bibliography notes, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Notes: Bibliography note cards, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Notebooks: III, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Notebooks: IV, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Notebooks: VI Lagos - Porto Novo 1889, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Notebooks: VII Dahomey, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Notebooks: Dahomey notes, 1971, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 25-26)
  - Notebooks: IX Kingdoms, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Notebooks: Evanston notes I, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Notebooks: F.O.M. I, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Notebooks: F.O.M. II, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Notebooks: F.O.M. III, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Notebooks: M.A.E. II and Dodds (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Notebooks: M.A.E. III: Hanotaux, Waddington, Ganier, Delcassé, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Notebooks: M.A.E. and P.R.O. VIII (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Notebooks: Marine, Waddington, Ribot, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Notebooks: Bibliography, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Series X. Audio and Visual Materials
  - Maps
    - (5) Maps of Africa (Northwest, East, West, Southern, Central) and a world map, 1963-1973, n.d. (Folder 2)
    - (6) Maps of Africa (Sierra Leone, Nigeria, Ibadan, Ghana, South Africa), 1968-1977, n.d. (Folder 3)
    - (8) Maps of Africa, n.d. (Box 36)
    - (2) Original map drawings used in Obichere's book West African States, 1971 (Box 36)
    - (12) Photocopied maps of Africa, n.d. (Box 36)
  - Photographs, Slides, and Postcards
    - Photographs: Boniface Obichere, 1959, 1972, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Photographs: Boniface Obichere - publicity photo, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Photographs: Boniface Obichere at the 2nd Ordinary Congress of the Association of African Historians, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Photographs: Boniface Obichere and John Mbiti (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Photographs: A party - some images show Obichere, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Photographs: Obichere's female PhD students, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Photographs: Chinua Achebe, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Photographs: Jackie Joyner (Kersee), autographed, with folder, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Photographs: Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., n.d. (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Photographs: James Washington, L.A. Rams #37, autographed, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Photographs: Black History Week Display, Hughes Aircraft Company, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Photographs: Florida, a party, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Photographs: Togo and Togoville, Africa (with negatives), 1963(?) (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Photographs: Map "Aequatorial-West-Afrika" (negative), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Photographs: Unidentified - horses, a beach, a picnic, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Photographs: Unidentified people, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Photographs: Unidentified people, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Photographs: Unidentified women, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Slides: France, n.d. (Box 33)
    - Slides: Italy (general), Florence, n.d. (Box 33)
    - Slides: Rome, n.d. (Box 33)
    - Slides: Slide show, n.d. (Box 33)
    - Slides: Steve Harmon's slides taken in Mali, with identification list, 1991 (Box 33)
    - Slides: Miscellaneous/Unidentified, 1960-1979, n.d. (Box 33)
    - Slides: Maps, n.d. (Box 33)
    - Postcards: Artwork, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Awujale of Ijebu-Ode, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Biafra, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Booker T. Washington Insurance Company, Alabama, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Dahomey, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Forum, Rome, Italy, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Ghana, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Hotel Stratford, Washington, D.C. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Mozambique, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Nantes, France, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Nigeria, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Oxford, United Kingdom, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Paris, France, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Senegal, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Postcards: Tiger, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)